{fs50c&#008008&3c&FFE87C&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}rights
{fs50c&H000000&3c&H000000FF&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}
|{fs50c&#H0000003c&ffffff&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}|{fs50c&H000000&3c&
H00FFFF&4c&I Typesettingfs40} Islam
Giza!Wei
{fs50c&#H0000003c&ffffff&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}|{fs50c&H000000&3c&
H000000FF&4c&I Typesettingfs40}|
<font color="# FF1122"
>"fb.me/eslamgiza2018 follow me on my
page official"
{the
UN-named company "decent" films offer
You adore listening to the horror
stories in my youth.
My sister (as much)
(And dear friend (Orhan
I
I used to sit to listen to the horror
stories that they see our forefathers
I used to scare my sister at night
under the blanket after hearing we
don't
Years passed, and I thought I'd tell
someone terrors that I have lived
I'm not good at writing
But I wrote my aunt lived its horrors
may relieve panic attacks what I
lived for(7) years
Twice (7) years since the reality
that the nakba
And, both tell her what happened
...tells me either it's a miracle
Or a great curse
I decided that both are true
I'm not sure where to end the curse
and where to start on
He (Orhan) my best friend.
(When I was four years old my sister
was born (as
(I was a close friend to(Orhan and
joined us (as much) as you grow up
Although (Orhan) wanted to get her
off in the beginning but their
relationship consolidation later.
After falling in love with each other.
Have some too much
Maybe more than our perception of a
cat
Then married years later.
{H00C0C0C0&3c&H00C
0C0C0&H00C0C0C0&I
Typesettingfs50b1}||
{H00C0C0C0&3c&H00C0C0C0&H00C0C0C0&I
Typesettingfs50b1}<font color="#
FF1122" >3
{H00C0C0C0&3c&H00C0C0C0&H00C0C0
C0&I
Typesettingfs50b1}see{H00C0C0C0&3c&H00
C0C0C0&H00C0C0C0&I Typesettingfs50b1}
||
{H00C0C0C0&3c&H00C0C0C0
&H00C0C0C0&I Typesettingfs35b1}"crime
of love"
{fs50c&#008008&3c&FFE87C&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}rights
{fs50c&H000000&3c&H000000FF&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}
|{fs50c&#H0000003c&ffffff&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}|{fs50c&H000000&3c&
H00FFFF&4c&I Typesettingfs40} Islam
Giza!Wei
{fs50c&#H0000003c&ffffff&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}|{fs50c&H000000&3c&
H000000FF&4c&I Typesettingfs40}|
<font color="# FF1122"
>"fb.me/eslamgiza2018 follow me on my
page official"
!(Did it again, (Khalil
You're a seasoned agent, we have
You know that smoking is prohibited
here.
There are a lot of flammable material
in this source
The gel does not drop, the city.
I'll watch out next time
No need for all this.
Well, you understand
I can't risk the safety of the client
for you
I have to fire you, collect your
stuff and go
Come on, Sir.
I'm in need of money to pay my bank
loan
Nothing I could do.
I apologize
I smoked a cigarette again?
I kicked his
!Wow
A man needs to work to pay off his
debts
I know, (women), what to do?
Do you offer work at risk?
No, not by hand trick actually
You have to stick to the mps
!Unfortunate
I'm going to the village to buy
school supplies for my son in the
morning.
Amount) has worked in the village as
well) so, I'll take her at 9 in the
morning, okay?
Well
Don't bother
See you later
Thank you
!There's something wrong with you
Nothing, my life
I had to fire an employee today.
Don't worry.
I'll get better as long as you're my
answer
You must be hungry, I made dinner
I'll come
Do you go out on a picnic?
You are saving the theme after dinner
mainly
Do we eat at "our Tree magic"?
Well
If we saw someone sitting here, we
will be crazy.
But no one knows that this is our
Tree magic
This tree brought us happiness
Was a witness to our happiness.
Brought us luck.
Tell your brother that it will be at
9 am
I told him you need to go to the
village.
No need to go early.
I'd like to go to the doctor just
isn't something urgent
What happened?
No need to worry
I'm going for the examination.
Any checking up?
That's why I wanted to come here.
I've always brought us this tree luck
Maybe I'll bring you some nice news
from the doctor tomorrow.
!(As much as)
!My heart
Husband (boyfriend) at the outside.
!He (Khalil) to commit suicide.
What do you say?
!(Aisha)
!You're the reason
!You're the reason in his suicide.
!Don't touch me
!God damn it
!Oh God, and pebble Black from his
work.
!Black of this clay so
!Come on, get up.
Muhammad), grew up in fourth grade)
Will be an engineer includes aircraft
!Well done
Sure he's smart and will teach in the
best universities
(I'll build a plane to go to my mom
(the king of
!My aunt
You came and saw the outline of the
plane?
Show me, spirit of my aunt
You stopped the car to go back to the
back seat?
Orhan) call)
Yes, (Orhan) is?
What do you say, (Orhan) is?
When did this happen?
Well, Brother, we're coming
What happened, brother? What did he
(Orhan) is?
!Watch
Black 3 moments
Black 3 moments in my life I didn't
want to remember her.
, the first
The death of my wife (the king) God's
mercy during the birth and she look
at me and despair overflowing from
her eyes.
"When he said to me, "I think our son
is good.
These were the last words I heard
from her.
, the second
Moments expressly the son before the
accident "!Help me, dad."
The call of God many not be the last
words I hear from my son
, the second
may be the most
"The moment see(as much) in the house
on "the Friday after the incident
several months.
Those nightmares haunted me, So come
the day of the "beauty" of this
Not nightmares may make the ordinary
man to afford it
{un
-named}"(on (Monday."
!(Honey (as much as
I was so scared to believe me
But everything will be fine, okay?
!Don't be afraid.
Mom, I'm out
Don't leave me (Muhammad) in the room
alone.
Where Are you going, son?
Get fresh air, I'll talk to you later.
Don't be late, okay?
I'll be back after an hour basically
{
fs35}(the king of yalu style) "from
1976 to 1997"
Do you forgive me?
I couldn't rely with our son.
I think it will recover soon
I think that God will help me
!(King)
Don't be mad at me.
{
fs35}(the property of what model) the
"read the bill on her soul."
Bought to see you in this dress.
While I was finality about awareness
Had a dream about you wearing this
dress.
What happened to me?
I don't remember anything.
You'll remember
I will help you to completely
I'll be with you always, don't worry.
I'll be with you.
I'll be with you always
I won't leave you
Is your son sleeping?
Reported by the bed, it must be that
Nam is currently
Sweet Dreams, son.
Is something wrong, son?
Nothing, mom, you can go back to
sleep.
Well
Good night, son.
Don't worry, over and over !Don't be
afraid.
I don't understand why.
!I found myself here all of a sudden
I'm so scared
Don't go down to the bottom.
There are bad memories in the bottom
you don't have to remember
If I recall, you won't count them out
!This closed the door to the
basement, don't even get to him.
Please don't tell this door.
Okay?
Don't try to open it and clean it up
My life
Come on, let's go to sleep.
I'll check the consequences of this
dog and come back, you wait here.
{un
-named}"(day (Tuesday"
What news of the Son of (frozen) for?
Are you talking to?
He can't Guard nor the dog
Sometimes I feel like he could move
his fingers a little.
God help you, brother.
Oh God, hurry to cure him.
Amen, inshallah
The manager (Orhan) distracted
recently
Fake heavy as well
It is tough you and me.
Lived through our very difficult days
I heard you guys don't talk to each
other.
Bon appetit.
Thank you, my brother, and BON
appetit to you
Thank you
!On the
outside, at the door.
!They will
they'll mind
woodsen. ideas poisoned
!They will
come to
offer to the madness
it poisons
the Son of
come to
pebble to him.
it's kill
the Son slows down severely
adhere to it
like bubble gum.
stretch his
brain like bubble gum.
it's the
host's son
Khadija)? a)
!Khadija), back to product)
(Khadija)
!Where Are you going? What you doin
this?
Come on, let's go home
!Is
You go and I'll be back later.
I'm fine, there is a task to get done.
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
I have a task to get done.
Let's get back to the house
(I have to talk to (Orhan
!Is
occasionally
talk to some of with our eyes only
I see your love
manifested for your eyes only
or when we hold
hands each other
I think to say
that our love for each other didn't
cause and that I love sons of Adam
the other.
used to say
that it is impossible to live one
without the other
(our love comes
from, (as much as
help recover
and remember me and love me as you
loved me in the arena
bought to see
you in this dress.
, while you
were unconscious.
had a dream
about you wearing this dress.
, when I gave
you that necklace was happiness, jump
out of your eyes and Leap.
(As much as)
!(As much as)
What happened?
They're mom and dad
I didn't face my mom on our marriage.
For this, I didn't talk to them a
while ago
Don't we have a picture of my father
I am?
(Orhan)
Orhan), and how long you will abstain
from risk?)
(Go from here, (the sword of
Get away from me and don't you come
to my house again.
!Go
I want you not to go out before you
tell me
And do not talk to anyone else, okay?
(Well, (Orhan
if you are a
star in the sky of our world
what you are
lighting the way for other
if my shares
activates your heart
prefer
blindness to happen to you.
Come on, son.
Have Department of sleep
Sweet Dreams
!O Allah, take care of and love.
!Don't take him from me never
Mom?
{un
-named}"(on (Wednesday"
Good morning, brother.
Good morning
Can we talk a bit, brother?
Orhan), I don't feel so good.)
I've been having hallucinations.
I cannot sleep
Last night I had nightmares alarming
again.
(You're my sister's husband and a
friend of my childhood, (Orhan
Don't push me away.
Your shift is about to start, get
back to work
!Orhan)! Listen, my brother)
You're blaming me, right?
You're right, it was my fault really
As much) expensive.)
Know that your wife beloved sister
(A guilty conscience every day to see
me, my son, (Orhan
Amount) don't avoid the nightmares
never will.)
"!I saw her last night also scream
"save me
(I missed him so much, (Orhan
Happen son me unable to move
Can't help his speech and movement
until the
I don't know what to do, what could I
do
I wish I could rewind time back, but
I can't
All my hands do is pray
!You the chance to play as well!
Enough
You're put away (as much) about me.
!Get away from me.
Get away from me or I will kill you
!I'll kill you.
Can you send some drawings?
Well, let's see some drawings
He grabbed a pencil
Let's start
See the drawing itself, okay?
Drawn by By
Remember?
Come on, let's see them
Is
Do you like this?
Well, let's
Hey
Wait
I'll be back immediately
The good son, what is there?
!I heard someone knocks the door.
I didn't hear anything.
Son?
Mohammed)? a)
Whenever the heart of the picture,
back as it was
Your eyes, benefit communications,
woman
!Stay upside down like that.
Let eyes Dog mauled.
Let eyes Dog
!Damn you, woman.
You deserve son
The heart of her again?
Do not reduce it again.
!But she's out of the picture
Who is it?
Welcome, my son.
Solved Hi, dad.
How are you?
Prefer
Are you okay? - Yes, Thank you.
Mom
Brown
Welcome
Sit down
Why didn't you bring your wife?
Didn't you want to come?
...I'll get it, mom, I'll get it.
Once you can
He says that his wife is sick.
Going to get them, when you talk to
her condition.
Come and introduce us
I love her, of course, bring it
Immediately come, I'll get it.
I'm going to prepare the tea
Well
Wash I hands
Wash it
!Wash it
You look troubled, my son.
I'm depressed as well
Do you go for the company (Fisk) for?
Will help us increase.
From (Fisk) this, MOM?
I can't expose my son to fight like
that.
I think it just, it need only care
Why are you here? Don't leave him
alone
You can go back to sleep, mom, I'm
here.
!(As much as)
Come with me.
I was always wandering when you're
asleep.
One night, I saw an old woman crying
here with two children
"I asked her, "what happened?
"And he said to me, "my daughter is
missing
I asked her where I lost her
specifically
They responded me saying that the man
standing next to the tree of their
"While referring to "our Tree magic
"was screaming desperately, "leave my
daughter alone.
And, while we look to replace the
reference
Choose the old man with the child in
a jiffy.
where is she
now?
Orhan) is?)
!(Orhan)
!I wake up, my dear.
Don't be afraid, the issue ended
No need to fear
!Over, baby, click.
{un
-named}"(day (Thursday"
!My brother (Saif)
Are you all right? Do you need
anything?
I'm fine, Thank you.
...Look at is your nature, if I can
help.
(Don't sleep, (able
I suffer from insomnia these days.
Frequency a lot of things in my mind
Mohammed) is fine as well)
Insha Allah solve all problems
Last year, my wife suffered from the
same problem
You can't sleep at night
She was trying to at home without a
goal
And, while a lot worse.
We decided to go to one of the elders
He told me to Paradise over her.
After her condition improved
thankfully
The UE thing (Fisk) a few Qur'anic
verses
The thing (Vespa) is?
You have to visit him, my brother.
I'll have my wife take you to him.
(I'll try, (able
Well, I'll talk to my wife to keep
you Company
And take (Muhammad) with you as well
Welcome
How are you, mom?
(Came in a pair (able
You told me that you have to go (to
the Shaykh named (Vespa
When she came to visit?
Come before you came a little
Said he's waiting for and she gave me
the address
Let's take the (Mohammed) and go.
(You stay here, and I(Muhammad
!(As much as)
You look beautiful verse
Glad your return to me as my husband.
(Don't you ever leave me, (Orhan
Would never leave you.
Look after you and protect you until
my last breath in
I'll take care of you.
I can't live without.
You're the only woman that I love
with my heart
Hey, my soul.
Is Mr. (Fisk) in the house?
Yeah, go ahead.
!(Hey you, (Muhammad
Where do you know my son?
I don't know, grandpa knew him and me
about it.
(Hey, my son (the sword of
I was waiting for you
(And welcome to you, (Muhammad
Come on, my granddaughter, would you
leave us alone?
Okay, grandpa.
(Sword)
You don't know me.
But I knew you were coming. yesterday.
I don't understand, Sir, how would
you know?
They showed me this
(I saw you and(Mohamed
Listen, son.
"The first wall of the Quran "bill
Invoice" means the beginning."
:In the first verse says "Praise be
to Allah, Lord of the worlds"
Means "praise" always belongs to God
, "As "the Lord of the worlds
(As explained by one of the
Companions of the Prophet (Abu ubaydah
That "worlds": they are wise people
who are
, Namely, 4 races
Human
Angels
Demons
Cheese
the devil
and the
You and your son hanging them Paradise
And since my son (Mohammed) weaker
than you.
They have the strongest
They are able to influence the more
obsessive you.
They do this to improve (Muhammad) to
me.
With the real is to communicate with
you.
Because they want to give you a job
to do.
Sir, I came to help you.
A guilty conscience is killing me.
I can't bear the pain that passes by
my son and I know that I'm the cause
of it
He's my only son.
I'll do my best to help
So, let your mind completely
Let's notice any "job" he wants her
brought them them.
Have someone sing them for more
information
Now, you can go.
Come to me tomorrow afternoon is
necessary
now, you can
go.
come to me
tomorrow afternoon is necessary
I will invite your brother and his
son for dinner tomorrow.
We will be happy like before all
!(Davut.)
!(Get up, (davut.
What happened?
!Get up
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
(Had a dream(Orhan
Go get it here
Come on, feed to sleep.
{un
-named}"(day (Thursday"
Go ahead, I'll watch
Sword), move my case bit by bit)
Excuse me if I have offended you
Do you come home for dinner and
you(Muhammad) is? I miss you so much
and God
Of course we'll come
I (Muhammad) to you lot too.
Everything will improve
What conditions (Muhammad) is?
He's fine, Thank you.
Insha Allah recover soon
Insha Allah
(I offended you so much, my brother
(the sword of no mind
Things had been rough on your hand
(Sword)
Do you come home for dinner and
you(Muhammad) is? I miss you so much
and God
Everything will improve and be happy
like before, right?
Well, my brother.
We'll be
Will (Muhammad) that also
If you don't mind, I'm leaving early
today.
We have an appointment at the doctor
Of course, my brother.
Will improve again.
In Sha Allah will be better anyway
Insha Allah
(Hello, aunt (kothari
!Seriously
!They came
, Repeat after me.
They're too weak mentally
I'm not very good at faith jealous
visual
(And they're not very good at
understanding, (Sword of
We can't talk to them as individuals
to solve the problem
They're whispering, we try to
understand them
There's a home to go every night, but
you can't enter him.
They would like you to perform the
task there
In the dead of the night
Wait in the room (Muhammad) till dawn
When you get the news, you go home.
You'll find the amulet like this, but
bigger
Burned and destroyed by the
You will see things strange and
sinister
But don't fear
Whatever happened to you from bad
stuff alarming
What you will see is nothing compared
to it
God help
I'll break your bones
I'll kill you and pluck out your eyes
!I'll kill you all.
I will rip your eyes all
I'll come to kill you all
You're going to die up here
Mom?
come, (Orhan) I
took your father !And to me, come
quickly
, in the
dead of the night
wait in
the room (Muhammad) till dawn
when you
get the news, you go home.
you will
see things strange and sinister
but don't
fear
, no
matter what happened to you from bad
stuff alarming
so what
you see is nothing compared to it
It's time, son.
(Go and saved (as much as
Go save her, dad.
!Mom
(I'm going home (Orhan
Sleep in a room (Muhammad) so do not
stay alone
!Good night, son.
!Dad
Dad?
Mom?
(Orhan)
!(Orhan)
you'll
find the amulet like this, but bigger
!Burned
and destroyed by the
!In the name of God
What did you do?
What did you do, (Orhan) is?
What did you do, (sword)?
!(Sword)
One fear in my place, why couldn't
the war you so
I was about to lose my mind, I
couldn't understand anything
I couldn't accept the facts that he
told me Orhan) later for a long time)
And, as mentioned already
There are 3 moments I remember in my
life.
, the first
The death of my wife (the king) God's
mercy during the birth and she look
at me and despair overflowing from
her eyes.
, the second
Moments expressly the son before the
accident "!Help me, dad."
, the second
may be the most
"The moment see(as much) in the house
on "the Friday after the incident
several months.
She died (as much) on the bus
I buried her myself.
But (Orhan) didn't accept her death.
Dig up her grave and took out her
body.
Taking the body home
According to that will His love for
her like she's alive.
But that wasn't enough for her.
Then, hold reading.
!I want it
!Saved me
from oppression
, I'm
ready to download anything
{to keep below
earth and heaven witness that I'll
send anything
!Saved me
from oppression
!I want it
, I'm
black. my death is inevitable
!Open the
door on it.
!Saved me
from oppression
{to keep below
earth and heaven witness that I want
it
!Black
Death inevitable
, I'm
ready to download anything
!Open the
door on it.
!Black
Death inevitable
!Open her
eyes
, I'm
ready to download anything
{to keep below
earth and heaven witness that I'll
send anything
!Saved me
from oppression
!Your
pocket its
!I want it
!He
concluded it
!Your
pocket its
!Saved me
from oppression
!Open her
eyes
!Saved me
from oppression
!He
concluded it
!Your
pocket its
!Black
Death inevitable
Detained Orhan one of the invisible
beings in a world that doesn't belong
(Forcing him to live in a body (much
like human beings
I think it
And I love her
Treat her like a kid that just opened
her eyes to a minimum
He wanted the entity to forget his
past (and live in this world like (as
much as
if I
remember those memories, you won't
count them out
OK?
...(From the overabundance of his
love for(as much as
Was satisfied with any thing on its
image, even if a freak like that.
Over time he began to be convinced
that this curse really his wife
So my invitation for dinner to see
her.
a sword),
would you come to dinner you
and(Muhammad) is?)
we'll be
happy with the same.
According to him, even the demons
smiling at her children next to her.
Enable (Orhan) of deportable based
mysterious
I didn't allow them to do
And avenge them by killing their
parents, despite the efforts (Orhan)
to protect them
I realized later that the nightmares
which she was having (not related
were talking to Joseph that he was
doing it (Orhan
(They wanted to guide me to the house
(Orhan to allow me to understand the
whole situation
Tried everything to restore their
daughter
Finally they made the thing a
mediator between us restore their
daughter to her world.
with the
real world is to communicate with you.
because
they want to give you a job to do.
The miraculous in Contemporary of His
is to restore his son (Muhammad) and
recovered after two weeks of that
night is dark
And regained his ability to walk and
talk again.
God cream
I believe that this is a living
example of God's mercy
Keep praying and will add you author
Disappeared (Orhan) after several
weeks
I never saw him from time.
Some said it went away
Some said he killed himself (to meet
his love (as much as
(don't you
ever leave me never, (Orhan
I'm not
leaving you no matter what happens
look after
you and protect you until my last
breath
I can't live
without you and you know this
Quote (Orhan) something forbidden,
cursed for his eternal love.
Recovered from another world.
I wear a being from another world,
the human body without the help of
any one
...Maybe
Didn't want to love anybody else.
{
fs35}(as one) "(from (1985) to the
(2006"
!(Orhan)
denied the letter
"R" The Marriage of the objects of
the non-human <font
color="#FFA500">"didn't mention
anything like that on the lips of the
Apostle." but scientists worldly life
and the sanctity of marriage, of
pounds, despite the impossibility of
it density question the mission "the
proportion saying of Allah in Surah
(the Romans) "of His signs is that he
created for you mates from among
yourselves,
and some sects and
religions recognized the possibility
of "marriage, human from non human
"side
and this things
does not share her health and her
fault entirely
{fs50c&#008008&3c&FFE87C&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}rights
{fs50c&H000000&3c&H000000FF&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}
|{fs50c&#H0000003c&ffffff&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}|{fs50c&H000000&3c&
H00FFFF&4c&I Typesettingfs40} Islam
Giza!Wei
{fs50c&#H0000003c&ffffff&4c&I
Typesettingfs40}|{fs50c&H000000&3c&
H000000FF&4c&I Typesettingfs40}|
<font color="# FF1122"
>"fb.me/eslamgiza2018 follow me on my
page official"
Automatic Translation By:
www.elsubtitle.com
Visit Our Website For Free Translation